Seventh Brother
Are you still happy?
Imperial Brother
You're not my husband
He went through great hardships to get medicine for you
What's wrong with repaying him?
It's not like this
This is
The Dragon Jade Treasure is with you
Heaven is truly helping me
Heaven helps me
Don't let your imagination run wild
As long as that thing doesn't happen
Nothing will go wrong
Back then, you were just like me
A pitiful person at others' mercy
You've really changed a lot
Highly skilled in martial arts
You don't seem as humble as before around Zhu Huaichen
And you've gained trusted guards
Moreover, you've saved me repeatedly
Could it be you've been reborn like me?
Zhi An
Don't be afraid, Zhi An
I'm here
I'll always be here
Steward Duan, what do you mean by this?
We have distinguished guests in the mansion today
The imperial consort is skilled in sword dancing
This is the most expensive ceremonial robe from Jinbao Zhai this season
If the imperial consort wears it to dance
She will surely shine brilliantly
Steward Duan wants our imperial consort to dance for the guests' entertainment
This is unacceptable
I'll go
The imperial consort is indeed more sensible
I remember she clearly made me wear shabby clothes
to attend the banquet
and made a complete fool of myself
Why would she prepare fine clothes for me now?
But coincidentally, that envoy from Western Region is quite lecherous
Zhu Huaichen arranged many beautiful maids to serve him
If I can attract his attention
Zhu Huaichen will surely offer me to the Western Envoy to secure the alliance
That will be our chance to strike him down
Huamei, help me get dressed
As you wish
Hah, Li Zhi'an
How I wish to chain you up
Forcing you to look at me day and night
And hate me
Huamei, assist me with my makeup
Yet you have no choice but to rely on me
Imperial Brother
Third Sister-in-law dancing alone seems rather dull
This younger brother volunteers to accompany with sword dance
I never knew Seventh Brother could perform sword dances
This is also my first time seeing Third Sister-in-law's graceful movements
Hence I was inspired to partner with her
Moved by genuine feeling
If I've caused any offense
I beg Third Sister-in-law's forgiveness
How could that be?